Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Manuscript Parts
  - "Free II" (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - "From this Moment On,” “From this Moment On,” “From this Moment On II” (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - "Games People Play" (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - "General's March" (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - "Gillette" (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - "Girl Talk" (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - "Go Go Cheer" (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "Go U Northwestern,” “Go U Northwestern II,” “Go U Northwestern II” (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "God Bless America,” “God Bless America II” (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - "God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen” (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - "Golden Arm" (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - "Good King W." (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - "Goody Goody,” “Goody Goody II,” “Goody Goody III,” “Goody Goody IV” (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - "Goofus II" (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - "Granada I,” “Granada II” (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Grand Old Flad” (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - "Greatest Rock Hits Page 1,” “Greatest Rock Hits Page 2” (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - "Green Berets" (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - "Green Giant Fite" (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - "Green Peppers" (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - "Green Onions" (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - "'Growing' Music" (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - "Hail Loyola" (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - "Hail Purdue,” “Hail Purdue II,” “Hail Purdue III” (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - "Hail State (Mississippi State Univ.)” (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - "Hail to Georgia II” (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - "Halftime Fanfare - 61” (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - "Hallmark Theme” (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - "Hark the Herald Angels Sing” (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - "Harper Woods Fite Song” (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - "Harry" (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - "Have a Coke and a Smile" (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - "Hawaiian War Chant,” “Hawaiian War Chant II,” “Hawaiian War Chant III” (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - "Head Medley" (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - "Heaven Knows" (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - "Hello Dolly" (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - "Here Comes the Showboat" (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - "Hernando's Hideaway" (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - "Hey Look Me Over,” “Hey Look Me Over,” “Hey Look Me Over II” (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - "Holiday for T-Bones" (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - "Homecoming Ceremony – Fanfare & My Beautiful Lady – P. 1,” “Homecoming Ceremony Page 2” (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - "Houston" (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - "Houston Fight Song" (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - "Houston Oilers" (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - "How High the Moon" (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - "I Could Have Danced All Night" (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - "I Got Rhythm Rock,” “I Got Rhythm Rock II” (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - "I Heard the Bells on Christmas Day" (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - "I Love a Parade" (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - "I Love Paris," "I Love Paris II" (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - "I Only Want to be with You" (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - "Illinois Loyalty," Illinois Loyalty II" (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - "I'm a Jayhawk" (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - "Impossible Dream" (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - "Indiana" (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - "Intermission Riff,” “Intermission Riff II,” “Intermission Riff III” (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - "Iowa on to Victory" (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - "It Came Upon a Midnight Clear" (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - "It's so Easy" (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - "Jazz Me Blues" (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - "Jazz Me Blues," "Silvery Moon" (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - "Johnson Rag II" (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - "Johnny Comes Marching Page 1,” “Johnny Comes Marching Page 2,” “Johnny Comes Marching II Page 1,” “Johnny Comes Marching II Page 2” (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - "Jolly Old St. Nicholas" (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - "Joshua" (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - "Joy" (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - "Joy to the World" (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - "Just in Love – A Band,” “Just in Love – B Band” (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - "Just One of Those Things" (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - "Kind of a Woman" (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - "King of the Road" (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - "Knock on Wood" (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - "Lamar Univ." (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - "Lassus Trombone" (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - "Lassus T-Bone" (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - "Lazy River II" (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - "Life is a Song" (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - "Light My Fire" (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - "Little Boat" (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - "Live and Let Die" (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - "Lola (Whatever Lola Wants)" (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - "Lover,” “Lover – Acc. Solo,” “Lover II” (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - "Lullaby of Broadway" (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - "Macarena" (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - "MacArthur Park Part I,” “MacArthur Park II P. 1,” “Macarthur Park II” (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - "Mack the Knife,” “Mack the Knife III” (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - "Malaguena,” “Malaguena – Current Used Verison,” “Malaguena II,” “Malaguena 72” (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - "Mame,” “Mame – 2,” “Mame – 3” (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - "Manhattan Skyline" (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "March America," "March America II" (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Marie" (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Masterpiece" (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "Mellow" (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Michigan National Theme,” “Michigan National Fanfares,” “Michigan National Waltz” (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Mickey Mouse March" (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Midnight Sun" (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Minerva Alma Mater" (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Minnesota Rouser" (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Mississippi Mud," "Mississippi Mud II" (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Monday, Monday" (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "Money—Money—Money" (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "Mongonucleosis,” Mongonucleosis II” (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "Moonlight Serenade" (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "Muppet Medley Page 1," "Muppet Medley Page 2" (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Musical Cheers II" (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "Musical Cocktail" (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Muskrat Ramble," "Muskrat Ramble II" (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "Must Be Jelly" (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - "My Life II" (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - "Name of the Game II" (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "Newscore – D" (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - "Night Train," "Night Train II" (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - "Night and Day," "Night and Day II" (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "Nittany Lion," Pennsylvania State (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - "Not from Dixie" (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - "Not Fragile" (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "Notre Dame II – Victory March” (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - "O Come All Ye Faithful" (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "O Little Town" (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - "O Tannenbaum" (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - "Ode to Billy Joe—Disco” (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - "Ode to Joy" (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - "Oh Babe!" (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - "Old Devil Moon" (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - "Old MacDonald" (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - "Old Man River,” “Old Man River – II,” “Old Man River – Vocal Arr.” (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - "Olympic Fanfare" (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - "On the Radio" (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - "On the Shelf" (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - "On Wisconsin," "On Wisconsin" (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - "Once in Love with Amy" (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - "One" (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - "Onward Christian Soldier" (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - "Operator" (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - "Opus #748" (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - "Our Director," "Our Director II," "'Our Director' Goes Pop" (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - "Patterns of Motion – Drill Music” (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - "Peanut Vendor," "Peanut Vendor II," "Peanut Vendor III" (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - "Pepsi Opener" (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - "Pregame Fanfares" (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - "Pregame Fight Song – Houston" (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - "Prelude II" (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - "Puff of Smoke" (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - "Put Your Hand in the Hand II" (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - "Raging Bull" (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - "Rah Rah for the Spartans" (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - "Rah Rah Rah for Kenton" (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - "Rebel Battle Cry" (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - "Red Cedar Drill" (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - "Red Cedar March" (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - "Revelli Fanfare" (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - "Reverse – Fight Song," "Reverse Fight Song" (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - "Rock A Bye Your Baby,” “Rock A Bye Your Baby,” “Rock-A-Bye Your Baby III” (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - "Round and Round,” “Round and Round II,” “Round and Round Again” (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - "Rice Fight Song" (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - "Rubberband Man" (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - "S.N.I. Theme" (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - "Saints I," "Saints II" (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - "San Francisco Fanfare" (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - "San Jose" (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - "Say it with Music" (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - "Schlitz" (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - "Senior Salute," "Senior Salute (Aud Lang Syne)" (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - "Service Medley" (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - "September III" (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - "Shanty (In Old Shantytown)" (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - "Silent Night" (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - "Sinfonia Fanfare I" (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - "Sing, Sing, Sing," "Sing, Sing, Sing II" (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - "Sing U.C.L.A." (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - "Skater's Waltz" (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - "Slaughter Page 1,” “Slaughter Page 2,” “Slaughter III P.1,” “Slaughter III P. 2” (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - "Slaughter on the Tenth Avenue – Page 1,” “Slaughter on the Tenth Avenue – Page 2” (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - "Slippery Rock Fight Song" (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - "Something for Cat II" (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - "Son of a Preacher Man" (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - "Sound of Music" (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - "Sound Off Chords" (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - "Soundpower Fanfares" (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - "South" (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - "South Rampart Street Parade Page 1," "South Rampart Street Parade Page 2" (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - "Spartan Drums" (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - "Special Events Music – Chorales” (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - "Spotlight Intros" (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - "Stand Up and Cheer" (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - "Star Spangled Banner - A♭,” “Star Spangled Banner - A♭” (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - "Star Spangled Banner - B♭” (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - "Star Spangled Banner – Fanfare (B♭)" (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - "Stardust" (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - "Stars and Stripes Ending" (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - "Stereo Fanfare #1" (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - "Stereo Festival Fanfare" (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - "Stranger in Paradise" (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - "Stripper," "'Stripper' (Short) & Texas Fite (Short)" (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - "Sunny" (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - "Superstar II, P.2" (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - "Swanee" (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - "Sweet Georgia Brown III" (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - "Sweet Georgia Rock" (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - "Sweet Sue" (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - "T.S.O.P." (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - "Tag #1" (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - "Tailgate Ramble," "Tailgate Ramble III" (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - "Tea for Two," "Tea for Two – Tap" (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - "Temptation II" (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - "Texas Fite" (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - "Texas, Our Texas" (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - "That Big Drum" (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - "That Old Black Magic," "That Old Black Magic II," "That Old Black Magic III" (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - "That’s My Baby,” “That’s My Baby,” “That’s My Baby – II” (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - "The Future Farmer" (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "The King II" (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "There's No Biz Like Show Biz" (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "They're Playing My Song" (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "This is My Country," "This is My Country II" (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Tiger Rag Page 2,” “Tiger Rag II” (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Tijuana Fight Song" (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "To Be Redeemed" (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Toot-Toot-Tootsie,” “Toot-Toot-Tootsie II” (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Up on the Housetop" (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Up Up and Away" (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "Varsity Drag," "Varsity Drag" (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - "Victors (U of M)" (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Victory March (Notre Dame)," "Victory March II" (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "W.S. Tag" (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Washington – B.C.D.” (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "Wassail Song" (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "We Three Kings" (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - "Well Get It," "Well Get It II" (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - "West Campus Fight Song" (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - "What Child is This" (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - "Whipped Cream" (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - "Whistle Cheer" (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - "Wildcat Victory (Kansas State U.)" (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - "Witchcraft" (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - "Woodchopper's Ball" (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "Work Song," "Work Song II," "Work Song Tag #2" (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - "Wrigley Spearmint Gum" (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - "Yea Alabama" (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - "Yellow Submarine" (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - "You'll Never Walk Alone" (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - "Zing," "Zing II" (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - "Zip – Vocal Arr.” (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Untitled E♭Horn part (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Moffit’s Resource Materials and Michigan State Band Books
  This series includes music books and show books from Michigan State University. It is arranged alphabetically and consists of 19 folders. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - 1000 Solos for the Drum Set; Vol. 1; Miller, Al (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Block Formation Drill; Casavant, A.R., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Block Progressions; Casavant, A.R., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Drum Ensembles for All Occasions, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Field Entrances; Casavant, A.R., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - The High School Band Clinic: Tested Drills and Exercizes That Improve Performance; Butts, Carol M., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Intermediate to Advanced Line Drills; Luethy, Ralph (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Phalanx Drill Movements; Casavant, A.R., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Precision Drill; Casavant, A.R., 1957 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Precision Drill Line Movements; Casavant, A.R., 1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Precision Drill Squad; Casavant, A.R., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Precision Drill Team; Casavant, A.R., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Precision Flash; Casavant, A.R., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Pre-Season 1982; The Michigan State Spartan Marching Band (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Pre-Season 1982; The Michigan State Spartan Marching Band (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Show Band Perspective Plotting Chart Handbook; Mills, Robert (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - “Sound Advice School Department Salute”; McCrom, Ray (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Spartan Marching Band Showbook; Michigan State University (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Spartan Marching Band; Michigan State University; 1964 Showbook (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Original Moffit Working Scores
  This series consists of William C. Moffit’s original scores to his marching band arrangements. The series is arranged alphabetically according to its original order and includes 11 boxes. Oversized working scores can be found in OVS Box 61. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - “6 The Leader” (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - ABC Monday Night Football (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - “Across the Field” (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - “Action Fanfares” (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - “Adj. Call” (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - “Aggie Fight Song” (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - “Ajax” (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - “Alabama” (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - “Alabama Jubilee” (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - “Alaska” (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - “Alexander’s Ragtime Band” (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - “All American Girl” (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - "Alma Mater”; UH, Fall 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - “Alma Mater”; Zanesville, Ohio (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - “A Lot of Livin’ to Do II”; Brass (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - “All I Ever Need is You” (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - “Alley Cat” (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - “A Lover’s Concerto” (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - “Aloutte” (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - “Always True To You In My Fashion” (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - “America” (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - “America” (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - “America the Beautiful” (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - “American Prelude” (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Amici; “Annieuse” (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - “Angels We Have Heard on High” (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - “Annie Lisle” (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - “Anniversary Waltz” (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - No. 8 “Anniversary” (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - “Another Opening, Another Show” (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - “Another Opening III” (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - “Anvil Chorus” (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - “April in Paris” (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - “A Quiet Gass” (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - “Arkansas” (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - “Arkansas Fight” (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - “Arizona State” (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - “Armed Forces Medley” (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Arranging Sketch Sheets (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - “Arron Intros”; “UA Fanfares” (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - “Artistry in Rhythm” (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - “A Shot in the Dark” (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - “A Taste of Honey” (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - “A Trumpet’s Player” (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - “No. 13 Auld Lang Syne” (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - “Auld Lang Syne – Farewell” (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - “Auld Lang Syne” (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - “Auld Lang Syne – Chorale and March” (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - “Anthony Wayne H.S.” (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - “Auld Lang Syne March” (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - “Austria Hymn” (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - “Away in a Manger” (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - “A.W. Fanfare” (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - “Back With a Beat” (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - “Back Home in “F” (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - “Back Home in Indiana – Fanfare” (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - “Baker” (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Ball State “Fight Team Fight” (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Band Books; Inside Rear Cover (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Band Catalog and Reference Scores (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - “Band Day Buffet” (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - “Band Intros” (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - “Band Taps” (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - “Bandorama Show” (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Basic Cadences Using the Single Stroke (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - “Basin Street Blues”, May 2, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - “Bass Clarinet Polka” (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - “Battle Hymn of the Republic”, September 10, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - “Baubles, Bangles, and Beads”, November, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - “Baubles, Bangles, and Beads II”, November 7, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - “Baubles, Bangles, and Beads III”, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - “Beatles Medley”, March 31, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - “Baylor” (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - “Beer Barrel Polka”, February 28, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - “Begin the Beguine” (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - “Begin the Beguine – March”, October 1969 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - “Bell Fanfare” (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - “Berceuse and Finale” (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - "Big Ten Medley” (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - “Big Ten Salute” (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - “Big Spender”, July 29, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - “Big Noise” (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - “Bilbao Song”, October 2, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - “Bill Bailey” (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - “Bill Bailey’s Combo” (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - “Bill Bailey Stomp” (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - “Birthday Chorale and March” (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - “No. 1 Birthday Present” (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - “Bittersweet Samba”, January 21, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - “B.J. and the Bear” (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - “Back Home Fanfare” (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - “No. 18 Blest Be the Tie” (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - “Blest Be the Tie That Binds” (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - “Block Band ABCD Drills” (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - “Blues in the Night”, October 23, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - “Boiler Blast Off”, October 16, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - “Boogie Blues”, October 1960 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - “Boogie Down”, December 28, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - “Boomer Sooner” (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - “Born Free”, January 13, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - “Bowl – Birthday Fanfare” (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - “Brandy” (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - “Brazil”, March 1971 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - “Buck Dance” (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - “Buck-Eye Battle Cry”, October 11, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - “Buck-Eye Fanfare” (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - “Bud Special”, November 27, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - “Bugler’s Dream” (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - “Butler War Song” (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - “But Not For Me”; September 21, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - “Cadence Fanfares” (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - “Caissons Song”, September 12, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - “California” (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - “California Dreamin”, November 16, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - “California Fight Song”, November 10, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - “California Here I Come” (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - “Calling Occupants” (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - “Campus Chime” (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - “Can Can”, October 1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - “Canfield Fight”; Brass and Percussion Score (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - “Canfield Fight”; Woodwinds Score” (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - “Cardinal Fight” (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - “Cardinals Intros-Canfield Fight”; Part Masters (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - “Cardinals Intros”; Brass and Percussion Score (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - “Cardinal Intros”; Woodwinds Score (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - “Carioca” (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - “Car Wash” (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - “Carmen” (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - “Carolina Victory”, September 1962 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - “Carousel Waltz” (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - “Carousel Waltz”, December 7, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - “Car Songs” (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - “Cartoon Music” (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - “Cav. Song”; University of Virginia, December 24, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - “CBS Sports College Football Theme” (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - “Cecilia” (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - “Ceremonial Procession” (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - “Change Music” (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - “Chappell’s Army Journal” (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - “Charleston” (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - “Cheerleader Intros” (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - “Cheerleader Intros” (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - “Chester” (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - “Chester” (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - “Chicago Loyalty” (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - “No. 7 Chow Call” (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - “Christmas Hail” (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - “Christmas Parade March” (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - “Clark Gum Shuffle” (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Circus Entry “Entry of the Gladiators” (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - “Clean Sweep” (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - “Cohan Salute” (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - “Coke Theme II” (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - “Cole Porter” (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - “Colgate” (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - “Colonel Bogey” (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - “Colorado” (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - “Come Back to Me” (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - “Come Join the Band” (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - “Comedian’s Gallup” (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - “Coming Up Roses”, November 28, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - “Concert Opener” (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - “Connecticut” (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - “Conquest”, September 1980 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - “Conquest Entry” (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - “Conquest Fanfare” (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - “Conquest” from “Captain from Castile” (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - “Cotton-Eyed Joe”, December 26, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - “Cougar Power”, November 10, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - “Cougar Song” (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - “Court Intros”; Homecoming Intros (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - “Court Intros”; Homecoming Intros (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - “Crazy Rhythm”, October 3, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - “Crea Mi Amor” (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - “Cumana”, February 1975 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - “Cumana” (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - “Cute”, September 14, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - “Cymbals Intro”, September 7, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - “Dancing in the Dark” (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - “Deck the Halls” (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - “Deep in the Heart of Texas” (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - “Delaware” (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - “Delphi” (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - “DePaul University Fight Song” (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - “Different Worlds” (79) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - “Dixie Cup”; B-D-2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - “Dixie Cup”; B-D-2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - “Doll Intros” (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - “Donkey Serenade”; B-D-1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - “Donkey Serenade”; B-D-1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - “Don’t You Hear the Lion’s Roar?” (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - “Double Eagle Fanfare” (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - “Double Mint Gum” (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "Down the Field” (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "Down the Field” (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - “Dr. Who ‘Hey’ So (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - “Dragnet” (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - “Dream”; Brass (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - “Dream” (Box 15, Folder 21)